<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Your awesome title</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>http://127.0.0.1:4000//</link>
    <atom:link href="http://127.0.0.1:4000//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 15:30:45 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 15:30:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sample Post</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;tote-bag-pork-belly-godard-meggings-xoxo-fanny-pack&quot;&gt;Tote bag pork belly godard meggings XOXO fanny pack.&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;## Plaid lumbersexual poutine keytar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lumbersexual butcher pabst pitchfork, forage readymade celiac neutra umami franzen chartreuse sartorial mlkshk blue bottle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Post-ironic man braid cornhole, VHS church-key kitsch pour-over irony banh mi wayfarers. Bicycle rights tumblr crucifix biodiesel 3 wolf moon kombucha. Ugh ethical&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;franzen, schlitz cray cardigan hashtag. Church-key chicharrones jean shorts, banjo tumblr swag lomo hammock vegan readymade echo park forage 8-bit literally flannel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id=&quot;test&quot;&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/sample-post-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Alt text&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/sample-post-2.png&quot; alt=&quot;Alt text&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/sample-post-3.png&quot; alt=&quot;Alt text&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h1 id=&quot;another-test&quot;&gt;Another test&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Knausgaard cold-pressed kinfolk 8-bit occupy. Chillwave humblebrag intelligentsia wolf marfa, put a bird on it lumbersexual irony post-ironic taxidermy tilde ennui quinoa heirloom trust fund. Swag slow-carb meditation street art cold-pressed, lumbersexual affogato authentic chartreuse try-hard hammock wolf chambray DIY. Brooklyn kale chips locavore hoodie, tote bag cornhole shoreditch actually portland banjo mixtape chambray quinoa forage. Pickled listicle letterpress health goth hashtag swag. Godard cornhole iPhone microdosing flexitarian, ethical scenester pop-up. DIY craft beer authentic, YOLO kitsch gluten-free offal shoreditch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/posts/sample-post-splash.png&quot; alt=&quot;Alt text&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aesthetic kale chips knausgaard, vinyl 3 wolf moon ethical selvage crucifix sustainable farm-to-table wolf. Wayfarers bicycle rights meh, lomo pug retro etsy flannel knausgaard artisan scenester austin selfies. VHS cray aesthetic trust fund organic. Fingerstache 3 wolf moon knausgaard chambray. 8-bit messenger bag meditation, brooklyn food truck cornhole kinfolk pour-over williamsburg readymade. Cronut shabby chic listicle, tousled mustache thundercats YOLO squid iPhone locavore. Ugh readymade echo park seitan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Schlitz master cleanse beard, flexitarian butcher chicharrones green juice lumbersexual scenester gastropub yuccie salvia put a bird on it. Gochujang squid chillwave shoreditch kinfolk chia. Hella lomo master cleanse etsy. Chillwave mlkshk umami gentrify craft beer fashion axe. Everyday carry waistcoat stumptown echo park gastropub, neutra shoreditch locavore. Kombucha cray before they sold out beard. Lo-fi raw denim pinterest, freegan whatever tumblr echo park chillwave craft beer blue bottle ramps brooklyn.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 17:14:08 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://127.0.0.1:4000//case-study/2016/03/02/sample-post-one.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://127.0.0.1:4000//case-study/2016/03/02/sample-post-one.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>case-study</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>sovrn UI and Design Patterns</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;a-weekend-to-pivot&quot;&gt;A weekend to pivot&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;January 14th, 2014, one coworker and I were let in on a secret — the company formerly-known-as-Lijit-and-then-Federated-Media was selling the brand + conversational marketing platform and was rebranding itself over the weekend.
Marketing had been working with Angry Bovine studios secretly to develop the branding and messaging up till that point. It was up to me and two other teammates to make app-wide changes to the old platform, as well as develop a brand new one-page site announcing the sell and rebranding of Federated Media as sovrn Holdings Inc. Due to the sensitive nature of the changes, we had to do it quietly and ready for the Monday announcement.
Jay Farracane provided the PSDs for the branding and designs for the Desktop version. I designed the mobile version and coded both over a hush-hush, sleepless weekend&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;22 hours over a Saturday and Sunday, and about 10 French presses later, it was finished.
After the dust settled, the sell-off went through and I took a nap, it became apparent that there was a lot of work to do.
We were mid-project on a complete app redesign based on the old brand. Hundreds of hours in design, feedback, and research had to be completely rethought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I decided the first step was the Weekly Stats Email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The untouched Weekly Stats Email (left) and the pilot that was currently in-design (right).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We were using that to pilot some of the comparative analytics Aaron Martin, Chris Newman and I had designed out as well as to clean up a lot of the visual language that had become so fragmented over FM’s decade-long lifespan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the rest of the app is an on-going process and launching soon, I’ll save a full unveiling for September. Hopefully these snap-shots will be enough to give an idea of the direction we’ve been developing and refining since January.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Style Guide for Tool Tip Treatment&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Earnings breakouts (left) and Ad Tag Editing Interaction (right)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the dramatic change was a huge boon to our process as what we were forced to rethink and redesign ended up being, in my opinion, so much better than our first run through.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 17:14:08 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://127.0.0.1:4000//jekyll/update/2016/03/02/sovrn-design-patterns.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://127.0.0.1:4000//jekyll/update/2016/03/02/sovrn-design-patterns.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
